

Husni Robani Full Stack Developer

- **Q** 082119802202
- https://github.com/husni-robani
- ♥ KOTA BANDUNG, JAWA BARAT

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

MBKM | Automation of notification system 02/2023 - 07/2023

- Designing an Entity-Relational Diagram (ERD) for the database application
- · Performing end-to-end application design
- Implement service pattern in backend using laravel action
- · develop an application that uses mvc architectural pattern
- implement many types of relation table database

Full Stack Developer

MBKM | Faculty accreditation system (SIAKRE) 09/2022 - 01/2023

- · Performing end-to-end application design
- · implement OOP in many services
- Implementation of ERD to database using laravel migration
- · Success to dealing development scope with client
- Success to implement authentication with many role and permission

Head of Organisation

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika (HIMATIF) 08/2022 - 08/2023

- · Led organization to achieve goals
- · organize many members
- learn to make many crucial decisions
- · learn to adapt to many types of people

EDUCATION

Informatics Engineering Widyatama University

SUMMARY

Currently an active sixth-semester student of Informatics Engineering Widyatama University. I have basic algorithm skills and knowledge of web development. I also gained practical experience in building scalable and efficient web solutions using technologies such as Laravel, and Vue.Js.

SKILLS

Laravel

Vue.Js

TailwindCSS

Inertia Js

Javascript

MySql

PHP

Java

Git